welcome guys my name is
if you are coming first time in on my
channel so my name is and i am a student
in some world and i'm doing network
so
i got very good response in my previous
videos and got a very positive reviews
from your side so that's why it makes me
motivate to make more videos with you
guys for you guys so that's why i'm
making a new video with new topic
so
let's start the video
uh today's topic is
very common like it's very demanded as
well
uh the topic is like how to change your
uh uh temporary lessons for me to a
student reference permit
like if you came in as a tourist and
you want to continue
as a student so how you will change your
uh your visa or you can see your
residence permit from
tourist sessions permit to assume that
transformer
so it's very simple like it's not uh
it's not that much hard
and it's not that much
complicated as well
likes
all what you want to do is like you have
to take an admission in school college
or university
and after that you just have to
take some documents uh let me share the
list of the documents with you guys
the list is uh
your insurance
like uh if you are if you want to do
undergraduate so you can also apply for
four years as well
like it's all depend on your degree uh
time period like if you are doing for
four years then you can apply your
instance from it for four years as well
and
if you're
if you're here for a high school and
it's for probably two years so you can
apply for two years as well so it's not
compulsory that you you will just
you just have a chance to apply for only
one year
so it's another point yeah so i was
there like individual insurance
you need to pay your tax
which is 125 turkish leader
and
you just need your passport your
insurance your tax
and
your biometric pictures
and your last business permit first copy
so that's all what you need so
like
like in every case not for
well not like less status in every case
university is doing it or university or
your school like you just have to go
there and you just have to take an
appointment first to change your
status from tourists to as uh touristy
guys inspiratory student reference
permit
after that they will make an appointment
and they will give you just a slip or a
form how can i say like that they will
give you the form
uh till you didn't get your card in that
form you your application number and
your all the details were mentioned
so
they will give you that and they will
submit your documents by yourself you
don't need to worry about it you just
have to submit your documents in the
university or school they will send it
to the coaching director
which is immigration office for the
foreign students or for our foreigners
so
after that you will get a message to
send your documents
on that date on that specific game
and it's also not concerned with you
they just send you the message because
you share your number and it's your
residence permit but the university or
school will do it
and after that you will get a message of
uh
of your
you will get the result message that you
your
relations permit application is
positively positively
concluded and after that the university
or
school will send you the
email or email that your residence it is
ready you can take it from my school or
college
so that's all uh it's so easy for you
guys if you want to
change your status from
touristic to students funding
and
some students are doing like
they are taking an admission in the
university but they are doing their
residence permit by themselves they
don't they don't want university or
school to involve in it so they are
doing very bad thing don't do like that
go with the university because it's easy
or it's fast way to get rid of uh to get
your
extension as well as the status change
from ballistic to the student entrance
permit
hope you guys uh like my video if you
like my videos so please subscribe my
channel and like my channel if you want
me to make more videos then please let
me know in the comments so or you can
approach me on instagram as well i
mention my instagram link as well so
[Music]
take care bye bye for till next video i
will see you next video bye